Guide to the Trinity College of Arts and Sciences, Office of the Dean records, 1911-2006 UA.25.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Container List
  - Faculty Benefits, 1975-1980 (Box 83)
  - Faculty, General, 1983-1984 (Box 83)
  - Faculty Newsletter, 1982-1985 (Box 83)
  - Faculty Participation in Appointment and Retention of Administrators, 1982 (Box 83)
  - Faculty and Salary Policies, Committee on, 1979-1980 (Box 83)
  - Federal Relations, 1984 (Box 83)
  - Federal Summer Intern Program, 1981 (Box 83)
  - Federation Advising, Task Force on, 1981-1982 (Box 83)
  - Federations, 1983 (Box 83)
  - Foreign Students, 1973-1982 (Box 83)
  - Forest History Society, 1984 (Box 83)
  - Forestry School, 1975-1984 (Box 83)
  - Founder's Day, 1980-1984 (Box 83)
  - Founder's Society, 1981-1982 (Box 83)
  - Franklin, Phyllis, Ace Fellow, 1980-1981 (Box 83)
  - Freshmen Innovative Seminars, 1982-1984 (Box 83)
  - Friends of the Library, 1982 (Box 83)
  - Fulbright-Hays Scholarship, 1983-1984 (Box 83)
  - Fundraising, 1981 (Box 83)
  - Fuqua School of Business, 1982-1983 (Box 83)
  - Fundraising, Committee on Incentive for Outside, 1980 (Box 83)
  - Gardens, Sarah P. Duke, 1980-1985 (Box 83)
  - Geography, 1980 (Box 83)
  - Geology Department, 1984 (Box 83)
  - Geology Planning Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 83)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1984 (Box 83)
  - German Planning Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 83)
  - Graduate Awards, 1983-1985 (Box 83)
  - Graduate Education in the Humanities, Ad hoc Committee on, 1980-1981 (Box 84)
  - Graduate Faculty Executive Committee, 1983-1986 (Box 84)
  - Graduate School, 1984 (Box 84)
  - Graduate Honors/Academic Standards, 1982-1983 (Box 84)
  - Graduation Lists, 1984 (Box 84)
  - Grant Applications, 1978-1981 (Box 84)
  - Grant Management Information System, 1982 (Box 84)
  - Green Fund, 1983 (Box 84)
  - Hard Money Committee, 1982 (Box 84)
  - Harward, Stephen C., Treasurer and Asst. Secretary, 1977-1979 (Box 84)
  - Health Affairs, Vice President for, 1981 (Box 84)
  - Health, Physical Education and Recreation, 1982-1984 (Box 84)
  - Helium Liquefier, 1980 (Box 84)
  - Hispanic Research Council, 1975-1979 (Box 84)
  - History Department, 1984 (Box 84)
  - History Planning, 1979-1984 (Box 84)
  - Hubbell Center, 1976 (Box 84)
  - Huestis, Charles B., 1975-1981 (Box 84)
  - Human Resources, 1983-1984 (Box 84)
  - Humanities Council, 1974-1984 (Box 84)
  - Humanities Department Chairmen, 1983 (Box 84)
  - Ibycus System, Computer-Classical S., 1982-1983 (Box 84)
  - Information and Regulation Bulletins, 1980-1982 (Box 84)
  - Information Systems, Vice President for, 1978-1984 (Box 84)
  - In-School Scholarship Committee, 1963-1984 (Box 84)
  - Institute of the Arts, 1982-1984 (Box 84)
  - Institute of the Arts, 1980-1981 (Box 85)
  - Institutional Advancement, 1969-1981 (Box 85)
  - Institutional Profile-Duke, 1980 (Box 85)
  - Internal Audit Office, 1982 (Box 85)
  - International Studies, 1984 (Box 85)
  - International Studies Planning Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 85)
  - Judaic Studies, 1979-1984 (Box 85)
  - Junior Science and Humanities Symposium, 1982-1983 (Box 85)
  - Latent Images, 1983 (Box 85)
  - Latin American Studies, 1983-1984 (Box 85)
  - Law School, 1976-1984 (Box 85)
  - Library, 1984 (Box 85)
  - Library Review Committee, 1983 (Box 85)
  - Linguistics, 1979-1984 (Box 85)
  - Linguistics, Executive Committee, 1980-1984 (Box 85)
  - Linguistics Planning Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 85)
  - Long-Range Planning Committee, Confidential, 1980-1982 (Box 85)
  - Long-Range Planning Committee Working Papers, 1977-1978 (Box 85)
  - Mac Anderson Scholarship Fund, 1982-1985 (Box 85)
  - MacFarlane Scholarships, 1984 (Box 85)
  - Majors Union, 1975-1981 (Box 85)
  - Marine Laboratory, 1984 (Box 85)
  - Mathematics Department, 1984 (Box 85)
  - Mathematics Planning Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 85)
  - Media Center for Library, 1980 (Box 85)
  - Mellon Proposal, 1976-1980, 1983 (Box 86)
  - Memberships, 1979-1984 (Box 86)
  - Metropolitan Life Foundation, 1981 (Box 86)
  - Mexico, Program in, 1982-1983 (Box 86)
  - Microelectronic Center of North Carolina, MCNC, 1983-1986 (Box 86)
  - Military Science, 1984 (Box 86)
  - Millholland, Donald W., Trinity Project, 1984-1985 (Box 86)
  - Minority Affairs, 1984 (Box 86)
  - Mu Beta Psi-Music, 1982 (Box 86)
  - Music Department, 1984 (Box 86)
  - Music Fees, 1980 (Box 86)
  - Music Planning Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 86)
  - Nathans, Elizabeth, 1974-1983 (Box 86)
  - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1977-1980 (Box 86)
  - NEH College Grant, 1980-1983 (Box 86)
  - National Humanities Center, 1984 (Box 86)
  - National Humanities Center Dinner, 1982 (Box 86)
  - National Humanities Center Fellows, 1985 (Box 86)
  - National Research Council, 1980-1983 (Box 86)
  - Naval Sciences, 1984-1986 (Box 86)
  - Neurobiology, 1981-1983 (Box 86)
  - New Faculty Orientation, 1984 (Box 87)
  - New Faculty Receptions, 1981-1982 (Box 87)
  - New Full-Time Faculty and Instructional Staff, 1982-1983 (Box 87)
  - N.C. Association of Colleges and Universities, 1974-1978 (Box 87)
  - N.C. Center for Independent Higher Education, Inc., 1976-1982 (Box 87)
  - North Carolina Central University, 1975 (Box 87)
  - N.C. Museum of Life and Science, 1982 (Box 87)
  - North Carolina State University, 1984 (Box 87)
  - Orientation, 1980-1984 (Box 87)
  - Outstanding Awards, 1982 (Box 87)
  - Paris Exchange Program, 1983-1985 (Box 87)
  - Philosophy Department, 1984-1985 (Box 87)
  - Philosophy Planning, 1984 (Box 87)
  - Physics Department, 1984 (Box 87)
  - Physics Planning, 1984-1985 (Box 87)
  - Placement Services, 1982-1985 (Box 87)
  - Political Science Department, 1984 (Box 87)
  - Political Science Planning, 1982-1984 (Box 87)
  - Pre-College Education, 1984 (Box 87)
  - Pre-Law Advising, 1985 (Box 87)
  - Pre-Major Advising, 1984 (Box 87)
  - President, 1984 (Box 87)
  - President's Associates, 1983 (Box 87)
  - Promotion and Tenure Committee, 1982 (Box 87)
  - Promotion and Tenure Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 88)
  - Promotion and Tenure Draft, 1981 (Box 88)
  - Promotion and Tenure Information, 1984-1985 (Box 88)
  - Provost, 1984 (Box 88)
  - Provost Planning Retreat, Blue Sky, 1983 (Box 88)
  - Psychology Department, 1984 (Box 88)
  - Psychology Planning Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 88)
  - Psychological Services Center, 1981-1982 (Box 88)
  - Public Education and Training of Teachers, University Committee on, 1974-1984 (Box 88)
  - Public Policy Studies, 1984 (Box 88)
  - Public Policy Studies Planning Documents, 1981-1982 (Box 88)
  - Public Safety, 1975-1984 (Box 88)
  - Quality Assurance Program, 1981-1983 (Box 88)
  - Race and Society Program, 1981-1983 (Box 88)
  - Reception, Arts and Sciences Support Staff, 1984 (Box 88)
  - Registrar, 1983-1984 (Box 88)
  - Registration Procedure, 1974-1980 (Box 88)
  - Religion Department, 1984 (Box 88)
  - Religion Planning Documents, 1984 (Box 88)
  - Research Assistantship Program, Undergraduate, 1981-1985 (Box 88)
  - Research Council, University, 1976-1984 (Box 88)
  - Research Support, Office of, 1984 (Box 88)
  - Residential Life, 1983 (Box 88)
  - Romance Languages Department, 1984 (Box 89)
  - Romance Languages Planning Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 89)
  - Rosati Fund, 1981-1982 (Box 89)
  - Round Table, 1980-1984 (Box 89)
  - Schedule Committee, University, 1975-1984 (Box 89)
  - Schondorf Exchange, 1984-1985 (Box 89)
  - Seminar on Aggression, 1984 (Box 89)
  - Slavic Languages and Literature, 1984 (Box 89)
  - Slavic Languages and Literature Planning Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 89)
  - Sociology Department, 1984 (Box 89)
  - Sociology Planning Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 89)
  - Space, Ad hoc Committee on, Arts and Sciences, 1985 (Box 89)
  - Space, Arts and Sciences, 1980-1983 (Box 89)
  - Special Students, 1984 (Box 89)
  - Statistics, 1980-1983 (Box 89)
  - Statistics, Ad hoc Committee on Undergraduate, 1980-1981 (Box 89)
  - Statistics and Decision Sci., Inst., 1983-1984 (Box 89)
  - Student Affairs, 1984 (Box 89)
  - Student Loans, 1975-1983 (Box 89)
  - Studio Art, 1983 (Box 89)
  - Study Rooms, 1979-1982 (Box 89)
  - Summer Session, 1984 (Box 89)
  - Summer Transitional Program, STP, 1984 (Box 89)
  - STP Advisory Committee, 1974-1985 (Box 89)
  - Supercomputer Committee, 1984 (Box 89)
  - Talent Identification Program, 1984-1985 (Box 89)
  - Technology and the Liberal Arts, 1984 (Box 90)
  - Telephone System, 1982-1984 (Box 90)
  - Title IX, 1976-1983 (Box 90)
  - Translation Service, 1980-1984 (Box 90)
  - Trinity College Distinguished Teaching Award, 1984 (Box 90)
  - Trinity College Consultant on Teaching, 1983-1984 (Box 90)
  - Trustees, 1984 (Box 90)
  - Trustee Lists, 1984 (Box 90)
  - Trustee Monthly Reports, 1984 (Box 90)
  - Tyler Prize, 1983 (Box 90)
  - University Marshall, 1980-1984 (Box 90)
  - Vienna Program, 1984-1985 (Box 90)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowships, 1983 (Box 90)
  - Women's Center, UNC/Duke, 1982-1984 (Box 90)
  - Women Faculty, 1983-1984 (Box 90)
  - Women's Issues League, 1983 (Box 90)
  - Women's Studies, 1984 (Box 90)
  - Women's Studies Mainstreaming Project, 1984 (Box 90)
  - You, Ms. Chen-Mei (Box 90)
  - Zoology Department, 1984 (Box 90)
  - Zoology Planning Documents, 1981-1984 (Box 90)
  - Academic Support Program Proposal, 1980 (Box 91)
  - Academic Support Program, 1982-1984 (Box 91)
  - Admission of 14-16 Year Olds, 1982-1983 (Box 91)
  - Advising UFCAS Long Range Planning, 1983-1984 (Box 91)
  - Advising, 1974-1985 (Box 91)
  - Advising Project Harrison Report, 1974-1985 (Box 91)
  - Afro-American Studies, 1978-1984 (Box 91)
  - Air Force ROTC, 1980-1984 RESTRICTED (Box 91)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1976-1984 (Box 91)
  - Army ROTC, 1983-1984 RESTRICTED (Box 91)
  - Athletic Council, 1983-1984 (Box 91)
  - Brown University, 1984 (Box 91)
  - Bryan, Virginia, 1979-1985 (Box 91)
  - Degree Requirements, 1976 (Box 91)
  - Faculty in Residence, 1982-1983 (Box 92)
  - Foreign Language Study - Friedl (Box 92)
  - Harrison, Paul (Box 92)
  - Housing, 1977-1984 (Box 92)
  - Judicial Board Cases, 1977-1984 (Box 92)
  - Luce Professorships (Box 92)
  - Master Course File Project (Box 92)
  - Minority Affairs, Office of, 1984 (Box 92)
  - Nathans, Elizabeth, 1983-1985 (Box 92)
  - Naval Academy Conference, 1980-1984 (Box 92)
  - Navy ROTC, 1983-1984 RESTRICTED (Box 92)
  - Officers Education Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 92)
  - Pre-Major Center, 1983-1985 (Box 93)
  - Residcom, Borchardt Committee (Box 93)
  - Residential Program Fund Invoices and Receipts, 1984-1985 (Box 93)
  - Summer Transitional Program, 1984 (Box 93)
  - Trinity College of Arts and Sciences Staff Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 93)
  - Academic Calendar, 1974-1985 (Box 94)
  - Academic Council, 1984-1985 (Box 94)
  - Academic Facilities, 1984-1986 (Box 94)
  - Academic Priorities Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 94)
  - Academic Skills Program, 1980-1985 (Box 94)
  - Academic Space, 1981-1984 (Box 94)
  - Accelerated Combined Degree Program, 1982-1983 (Box 94)
  - Accounting Procedures, 1975-1985 (Box 94)
  - Admissions, 1985 (Box 94)
  - Admissions, Faculty Participants, 1979-1986 (Box 94)
  - Admissions Office Review, 1985 (Box 94)
  - Aerospace Studies, 1983-1985 (Box 94)
  - Aggression, Faculty Seminar on, 1984-1986 (Box 94)
  - Aging and Human Development, Human Council on, 1985 (Box 94)
  - Allen Building-Lobby, 1983 (Box 94)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1985 (Box 94)
  - American Association of Higher Education, 1976-1986 (Box 94)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1980-1984 (Box 94)
  - American Association of University Women Educational Foundation, 1981-1983 (Box 94)
  - American Council on Education, 1984-1986 (Box 94)
  - American Council on Life Insurance, 1983-1985 (Box 94)
  - American Dance Festival, 1980-1986 (Box 94)
  - American Schools of Oriental Research, 1980-1984 (Box 94)
  - American Speech, 1980-1985 (Box 94)
  - American Psychological Association, 1984 (Box 94)
  - Angier B. Duke, 1984-1986 (Box 94)
  - Annual Giving, 1983-1986 (Box 95)
  - Art Department, 1985 (Box 95)
  - Arts and Sciences Campaign, 1985 (Box 95)
  - Asian/Pacific Studies Institute, 1980-1986 (Box 95)
  - ASDU Legislation Minutes, 1985 (Box 95)
  - Association of American Universities, 1983-1984 (Box 95)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1983-1984 (Box 95)
  - Association of Duke Women, 1980-1981 (Box 95)
  - Association for Women in Science, Inc., 1983 (Box 95)
  - Athletic Council, 1983-1986 (Box 95)
  - Auxiliary Services, 1986 (Box 95)
  - BA/MA Program, 1982-1983 (Box 95)
  - Behavioral Sciences Center, 1985 (Box 95)
  - Benefits and Records, 1978-1986 (Box 95)
  - Mary Duke Biddle Foundation, 1982-1986 (Box 95)
  - Biological Sciences Council, 1975-1984 (Box 95)
  - Biology Major, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Biomedical Research Support Grants, 1984-1985 (Box 95)
  - Black Add-On Policy, 1983-1984 (Box 95)
  - Black Affairs, President's Council on, 1980-1985 (Box 95)
  - Black Faculty Appointments, Committee on, 1979-1980 (Box 95)
  - Black Faculty Recruitments, 1980-1986 (Box 95)
  - Black Faculty, University Committee on, 1982-1983 (Box 96)
  - Black Student Alliance, 1981-1986 (Box 96)
  - Bloom Endowment Fund, 1987 (Box 96)
  - Board Plan, 1980 (Box 96)
  - Bryan, Virginia, 1982-1987 (Box 96)
  - Bunting Fellowship, 1982-1984 (Box 96)
  - Bus, 1974-1983 (Box 96)
  - Business Auxiliaries, 1981-1985 (Box 96)
  - Business Manager, 1981-1985 (Box 96)
  - Business-in-Residence Program, 1985 (Box 96)
  - Byzantine Studies Conference, 1983 (Box 96)
  - Cable 13-DUCTV, 1982-1983 (Box 96)
  - Calendar, University, 1980-1985 (Box 96)
  - Canadian Studies, 1983-1985 (Box 96)
  - Carlyle Letters, 1979-1983 (Box 96)
  - Cash Management Policy, 1983 (Box 96)
  - Census Forms, 1983 (Box 96)
  - Chairmen, Arts and Sciences, 1983-1985 (Box 96)
  - Chancellor, 1984-1985 (Box 96)
  - Chronicle-Editor, 1974-1983 (Box 96)
  - Classical Studies, 1984-1985 (Box 96)
  - Collegiate Academy Lecture Program, Robert Sullivan, Coordinator, 1982-1985 (Box 96)
  - Comparative Literature, 1984-1985 (Box 96)
  - Computation Center, 1982-1986 (Box 96)
  - Computer Camp-DUCC, 1984-1986 (Box 96)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, COFHE, 1979-1986 (Box 96)
  - Course Schedules, 1983-1986 (Box 96)
  - Deans Conference, 1985-1986 (Box 96)
  - Deans Staff, 1983-1986 (Box 96)
  - Demographic Studies, 1980-1986 (Box 97)
  - Departmental Reviews, 1980-1982 (Box 97)
  - Development, 1984-1985 (Box 97)
  - Directors of Graduate Studies, 1979-1986 (Box 97)
  - Directors of Undergraduate Studies, 1984-1985 (Box 97)
  - Distinguished Professors, 1983-1985 (Box 97)
  - Distinguished Professor Seminars, 1982-1985 (Box 97)
  - Drama, 1983-1985 (Box 97)
  - Drama Committee, 1980-1984 (Box 97)
  - Duke/Durham Fellows, 1984-1985 (Box 97)
  - Duke East/West Program, 1983 [Duke Seminar] (Box 97)
  - Duke Endowment, 1984-1985 (Box 97)
  - Duke Power, 1984 (Box 97)
  - Duke Press, 1981-1985 (Box 97)
  - East Asia Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 97)
  - East Campus Library, 1982 (Box 97)
  - Engineering Research Center, 1984-1985 (Box 97)
  - Enrollments, 1981-1986 (Box 98)
  - Equipment, Renovations and Furnishings, A and S, 1981-1985 (Box 98)
  - Exchange Programs General, 1980-1986 (Box 98)
  - Faculty Association in Trinity College, 1983-1985 (Box 98)
  - Faculty Compensation Committee, 1981-1986 (Box 98)
  - Faculty Newsletter, 1986 (Box 98)
  - Faculty at Regular Ranks, 1968-1984 (Box 98)
  - Faculty Seminar on Aggression, 1984 (Box 98)
  - Fees, 1977-1986 (Box 98)
  - Film and Video Committee, 1980-1986 (Box 98)
  - Financial Aid, 1982-1986 (Box 98)
  - Food Services, 1975-1986 (Box 98)
  - Forestry School, 1985-1986 (Box 98)
  - Founder's Day, 1985-1986 (Box 98)
  - Freshman Clusters, 1981-1986 (Box 98)
  - Governor's Center, 1982-1986 (Box 98)
  - Human Development Program, Undergraduate Committee on, 1983-1985 (Box 98)
  - Humanities and Science Councils, 1984 (Box 98)
  - Incentive Plan for Arts and Sciences, 1983 (Box 98)
  - Institutional Research, Virginia Bryan, 1984 (Box 98)
  - Interdisciplinary History of Ideas, 1981-1987 (Box 98)
  - International Studies 3/2 Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 98)
  - Islamic and Arabian Studies, 1983-1985 (Box 98)
  - Judaic Studies, 1973-1985 (Box 99)
  - Judicial Board, 1982-1985 (Box 99)
  - Kellogg Fellowship, 1977-1983 (Box 99)
  - Klein Scholarship Fund, Andrew S., 1982 (Box 99)
  - Language Laboratory, 1983-1986 (Box 99)
  - Library, 1984-1985 (Box 99)
  - Marine Laboratory Advisory Committee, 1981-1985 (Box 99)
  - Mellon Fellowships in the Humanities, 1976-1986 (Box 99)
  - Methodist Board of Higher Education, 1980-1986 (Box 99)
  - Methodist Conferences of North Carolina, 1975-1976 (Box 99)
  - Neurosciences, Undergraduate Program in, 1979-1985 (Box 99)
  - New Faculty, 1984 (Box 99)
  - News Service, 1984-1986 (Box 99)
  - N. L. Industries Foundation, 1984 (Box 99)
  - North Carolina Board of Science and Technology, 1979-1984 (Box 99)
  - North Carolina Humanities Committee, 1980-1986 (Box 99)
  - North Carolina School of Math and Science, 1980-1984 (Box 99)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities, 1981-1986 (Box 99)
  - Outstanding Young Women of American, 1982 (Box 99)
  - Parent's Weekend, 1983-1986 (Box 99)
  - Parking, 1981-1985 (Box 99)
  - Physics Shop, 1985 (Box 99)
  - Preceptors, 1981-1984 (Box 99)
  - Presidential Young Investigators Awards, 1983-1986 (Box 99)
  - President's Program on Human Resources Effectiveness, 1984-1985 (Box 99)
  - Primate Center, 1983-1985 (Box 99)
  - Provost's Staff, 1984-1985 (Box 100)
  - Public Education and Training of Teachers, Univ. Committee on, 1984-1985 (Box 100)
  - Publication Information, 1983-1984 (Box 100)
  - Questionnaires and Surveys, 1976-1986 (Box 100)
  - Radio Board, 1984 (Box 100)
  - Residential Life, 1985 (Box 100)
  - Residential Program Funding Committee, 1985 (Box 100)
  - Scholarships and Fellowships, 1984-1986 (Box 100)
  - Science and Humanities, NC Junior Symposium, 1985 (Box 100)
  - Science Library, 1985 (Box 100)
  - Science Technology and Human Values, 1984-1985 (Box 100)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1981-1984 (Box 100)
  - Small Group Learning Experience, 1984 (Box 100)
  - Southeastern Universities Research Associates, Inc., SURA, 1982-1984 (Box 100)
  - Step Symposium Committee, 1984 (Box 100)
  - Student affairs, 1985 (Box 100)
  - Student Awards, 1985 (Box 100)
  - Study Abroad General, 1984-1985 (Box 100)
  - Summer Seminars for College Teachers, 1984 (Box 100)
  - Summer Transitional Program STP, 1985-1987 (Box 100)
  - STP Advisory Committee, 1986 (Box 100)
  - STP/ASP Summer Transitional Academic Skills Program, 1986 (Box 100)
  - Supplemental Pay, 1981-1984 (Box 101)
  - Talent Identification Program, 1986 (Box 101)
  - Teaching Council, University Wide, 1984 (Box 101)
  - Teacher Course Evaluations, 1984-1985 (Box 101)
  - Teaching Loads, 1984-1986 (Box 101)
  - Technical Support, University Committee on, 1982-1985 (Box 101)
  - Technology and the Liberal Arts, 1983-1985 (Box 101)
  - Tenure Study, 1985 (Box 101)
  - Transportation, 1985 (Box 101)
  - Triangle Universities Center for Advanced Studies, 1984 (Box 101)
  - Tropical Studies, Organization for, 1983-1986 (Box 101)
  - Truman Scholarship Program, Harry S., 1976-1986 (Box 101)
  - Trustees, 1985 (Box 101)
  - Trustees List, 1985-1986 (Box 101)
  - Trustees Monthly Report, 1985 (Box 101)
  - Tuition Charges, 1980-1986 (Box 101)
  - Uncleared Student Charges, 1980-1984 (Box 101)
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, 1981-1986 (Box 101)
  - University Relations, 1981-1985 (Box 101)
  - Veterans Administration, 1983 (Box 101)
  - Washington Duke Club, 1983-1986 (Box 101)
  - Winston Churchill Scholarship, 1982-1986 (Box 101)
  - Women's Majors, 1984 (Box 101)
  - Women's Network, 1984-1986 (Box 101)
  - Writer's Conference, 1982-1986 (Box 101)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, Board of Trustees, 1985-1989 (Box 102)
  - Academic Computing System, 1986-1988 (Box 102)
  - Academic Council, 1986-1989 (Box 102)
  - Academic Council, Minutes and Agenda, 1986, 1989 (Box 102)
  - Academic Council, 1985 (Box 103)
  - Academic Facilities, 1987-1989 (Box 103)
  - Academic Plan, Five Year, 1987 (Box 103)
  - Academic Priorities Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 103)
  - Academic Skills Program, 1986-1988 (Box 104)
  - Admissions, 1986-1989 (Box 104)
  - Admissions and Financial Aid, Advisory Committee on, 1985-1988 (Box 104)
  - Admissions and Financial Aid, University Committee on, Undergraduate, 1985-1987 (Box 105)
  - Advanced Placement, 1984-1986 (Box 105)
  - Advising General, 1984-1985 (Box 105)
  - Advising in the Health Professions, 1984-1988 (Box 105)
  - Aerospace Studies, 1986-1989 (Box 105)
  - Afro-American Studies, 1982-1986 (Box 105)
  - Aging and Human Development, Univ. Council on, 1986-1989 (Box 105)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1986-1989 (Box 105)
  - Alumni Affairs/Danube Trip, 1987 (Box 105)
  - Alumni Survey, 1986 (Box 105)
  - Alumni Travel, 1986 (Box 105)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1984-1985 (Box 105)
  - American Studies Program, 1986-1988 (Box 105)
  - American Telephone and Telegraph, AT and T, 1985-1986 (Box 105)
  - Angier B. Duke Memorial Scholarships, 1988-1989 (Box 105)
  - Angier B. Duke Memorial Scholarships, 1984-1987 (Box 106)
  - Annual Giving, 1987-1989 (Box 106)
  - Anthropology, 1985-1988 (Box 106)
  - Anthropology and Anatomy, Biological, 1988-1989 (Box 106)
  - Anthropology, Cultural, 1988-1989 (Box 106)
  - AP and T Costs, 1988 (Box 106)
  - ARLO, Action, Research, Liaison Office, 1984-1987 (Box 106)
  - Art and Art History, 1986-1989 (Box 106)
  - Art Museum, 1985-1989 (Box 106)
  - Arts and Sciences Campaign, 1986-1989 (Box 106)
  - Arts and Sciences Campaign Steering Committee Minutes and Agenda, 1984-1989 (Box 106)
  - Arts and Sciences Campaign, 1986 (Box 107)
  - Arts and Sciences Resource Allocation Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 107)
  - Asian and African Languages and Literatures, 1988-1989 (Box 107)
  - Asian/Pacific Studies Institute, 1987-1989 (Box 107)
  - Associate Dean, 1983-1989 (Box 107)
  - Associated Students of Duke University, ASDU, 1985-1989 (Box 107)
  - Associated Students of Duke University, ASDU Legislation Minutes, 1986-1989 (Box 107)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1987-1989 (Box 107)
  - Athletic Department, 1985-1989 (Box 107)
  - Authors, Dinner, 1983-1984 (Box 108)
  - Awards and Prizes, 1984-1986 (Box 108)
  - Basic Medical Science, 1987-1989 (Box 108)
  - Bates, Margaret, Vice Provost, 1985-1990 (Box 108)
  - Benenson Awards, General Correspondence, 1983-1989 (Box 108)
  - Benjamin N. Duke Scholarships, 1986-1988 (Box 108)
  - Berlin Exchange, 1985-1986 (Box 108)
  - Biddle Foundation, Mary Duke, 1987-1989 (Box 108)
  - Biology Major, 1987-1989 (Box 108)
  - Biomedical Research Support Grants, BRSG, 1986-1989 (Box 108)
  - Biotechnology Council, 1983-1988 (Box 108)
  - Black Affairs, President's Council on, 1986-1989 (Box 108)
  - Black African Studies, 1987 (Box 108)
  - Black Faculty Recruitment, 1988-1989 (Box 108)
  - Black Faculty Recruitment, 1987 (Box 109)
  - Black on White, 1988 (Box 109)
  - Blue Sky Retreat/Planning, 1985-1987 (Box 109)
  - Botany Department, 1985-1989 (Box 109)
  - Budget, 1986-1990 (Box 109)
  - Budget Forecast, 1987-1989 (Box 109)
  - Bulletin Information, 1983-1986 (Box 109)
  - Burger, Paula, 1986-1989 (Box 109)
  - Bursar, 1975-1986 (Box 109)
  - Business Auxiliaries, 1987-1988 (Box 109)
  - Cable 13 DUCTV, 1987-1989 (Box 109)
  - Calder Foundation, Louis, 1985 (Box 109)
  - Calendar University, 1987-1989 (Box 109)
  - CALICO, 1985-1986 (Box 109)
  - Campaign for Duke, 1989 (Box 109)
  - Campus Club, 1983-1984 (Box 109)
  - Canadian Studies, 1986 (Box 109)
  - Career Advising, 1987-1988 (Box 110)
  - Career Apprenticeship Program, 1987 (Box 110)